learnsocial.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy | LearnSocial

This web site is owned and operated by Way2Digital Private Limited ("we", "our", or "us" or the "Company") ("Way2Digital").We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy and to fight spam. This Privacy Policy (the "Policy”) describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide to us when you visit the LearnSocial web site (the "Site”) located at [www.learnsocial.com](https://www.learnsocial.com/). Please note that the primary purpose of our Site and the Services it to allow you to enroll in and take online courses on a variety of topics ("Courses”). For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, information that you provide through the Site can be in one of two categories: information relating to your use of the Site or the Services, including, without limitation, enrollment information for Courses, is referred to as "Site Information,” while information relating to taking the Courses, including, without limitation, interchanges with the Course instructors ("Instructors”), other students ("Users”), answers, essays and other items submitted to satisfy Course requirements, is referred to as "Course Information”. Our policies may differ from other service offerings and you should carefully review the terms of service and this privacy notice before using these services.

#### Note:

Our Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.

By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our website.

By mere use of the website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use.

#### Information we collect about you and how we use it.

Your information is the information that's required when you visit the site, as well as the information you choose to share. ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ refers to information by which you may be personally identified, such as your name, email address and phone number. You will need to register for visiting our site. If you choose to register, and are 18 years of age or older, you are required to provide personally identifiable information such as your name, email address and phone number. The personally identifiable Information you submit to receive information and Services from our site will never be disclosed to any third party. We do not collect more Information than is reasonably necessary to participate in an activity on the Websites.

You allow us to use this personally identifiable Information to register you to use the Services, enroll in Courses, and otherwise provide you with the Services; verify your authority to enter the Site and access the Courses and Services; notify you of updates; improve the content and general administration of the Site and the Services; provide you with notices regarding the Services and other services that you have purchased or may wish to purchase in the future.

You also consent to our providing this personally identifiable information to Instructors as part of the Course Information when you enroll in a Course. Instructors will use this Course Information to provide the Course to you. Instructors may have other users for Course Information. It is your responsibility when you enroll in a Course to confirm what uses the Instructor will make of your personally identifiable Course Information. Way2Digital does not control these uses by Instructors.

#### Other Information We Collect and How We Use It:

Way2Digital may also automatically collect and analyze Site Information about your general usage of the Site, Services and Courses. We might track your usage patterns to see what features of the Site, Services and Courses you commonly use, Site traffic volume, frequency of visits, type and time of transactions, type of browser, browser language, IP address and operating system, and statistical information about how you use the Services and Courses. We only collect, track and analyze such Site Information in an aggregate manner that does not personally identify you. This aggregate data may be used to assist us in operating the Site and the Services and provided to other third parties to enable them to better understand the operation of the Services, and improve their Course offerings, but such information will be in aggregate form only and it will not contain personally identifiable data.

Instructors may collect non-personally identifiable Course Information in connection with your participation in Courses. This Course Information may include, but not be limited to, your interaction with the Instructor and other Users, comments you leave on Course forums, answers or essays you submit to satisfy Course requirements, and so forth. As noted above, it is your responsibility to review the Instructor’s policy in connection with all Course Information and decide whether or not you want to provide such Course Information.

#### Children's Privacy

We are committed to protecting children's privacy online. This Site is intended for users above the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect information from children.

#### Updating or Deleting of Personally Identifiable Information:

For any update or deletion of your personally identifiable information please email us at [experience@learnsocial.com](mailto:experience@learnsocial.com)

#### Billing:

If you use or provide services on the Site for which we implement a billing system for you, we will collect additional information from you so that we can process and collect billing information. For example, we may collect your mailing address to remit payments.

#### Cookies:

When you use our Websites we may use cookies and other technologies in order to facilitate and customize your use of our Services.

#### What is a cookie?

A cookie is a small data text file, which a website stores on your computer or mobile device (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us.

Our cookies store randomly assigned user identification numbers, the country where you are located, and your first name to welcome you back to our Websites. The cookies make your use of the Websites easier, make the Websites run more smoothly, and save your logged-in state so that you do not have to log in each time that you visit the Websites.

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company and service providers, is not covered by our Privacy Policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, and service providers, use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the shopping cart, etc.

You can disable and/or delete all types of cookies by using your browser settings. Cookies are generally easy to disable and/or delete but how you do so varies from browser to browser. The "help” function within your browser should tell you how to do it. The best way may be to close your browser and then search for "cookie folder” or "cookie manager” or simply "cookie”. Please also visit [](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)www.allaboutcookies.org for more information about cookies and how to disable them. If you do disable cookies, our Websites will not recognize you and you may not have access to all portions of the Websites.

#### Disclosure of Information:

We will share your personally identifiable Site Information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. Please refer to the sections above on personally identifiable and other Course Information for how Course Information may be used.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable Information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure doing so in the Company's interest to protect its property or other legal rights or the rights or property of others.

We may also disclose your personally identifiable information: (a) to enforce these Terms of Use or (b) to protect the safety of Users of our Site and our Services and Courses. In addition, we may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization.

#### Retention of Information:

We will keep personally identifiable Information of our users for as long as they are registered subscribers or users of our products and services, and as permitted by law.

## Data Security:

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology.

To make online purchases you must use an SSL-enabled browser in order to protect the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it is transmitted over the Internet.

Access by you to your account is available through a password and/or unique user name selected by you. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone, that you change your password often using a combination of letters and numbers, and that you ensure you use a secure web browser. We cannot be held accountable for activity that results from your own neglect to safeguard the secrecy of your password and user name. If you share a computer with anyone, you should always log out of your account after you are finished, in order to prevent access to your information from subsequent users of that computer.

Please notify us as soon as possible if your user name or password is compromised. Call to: +91 - 8184845555 for assistance, or email [experience@learnsocial.com.](mailto:experience@learnsocial.com.)

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Website cannot be guaranteed and we shall have no liability to you or any third party for loss, misuse, disclosure or alteration of such information; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party.

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personally Identifiable Information in our control may have been compromised, we will notify you as promptly as possible under the circumstances. To the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail and you consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification. If you prefer for us to use another method to notify you in this situation, please e-mail us at [experience@learnsocial.com.](mailto:experience@learnsocial.com.) with the alternative contact information you wish to be used.

#### Linking:

This Site may contain links to other web sites. The Company cannot and does not control the privacy practices of any such sites. You should review the privacy policy on any web site where you may submit personal information before providing it to any web site.

#### International Users:

This Site is hosted and operated in the India. If you are visiting from other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from Indian law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to India, which does not have the same data protection laws and by providing your personal data you consent to:

  * The use of your personal data for the uses identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and
  * The transfer of your personal data to the India as indicated above.

#### Contact Us:

_If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, please contact us by emailing[experience@learnsocial.com](mailto:experience@learnsocial.com.)._

**WAY2DIGITAL PRIVATE LIMITED**  
Level-3, Vamsiram Jubilee Casa,  
Plot No 1246, Road No 62,  
Jubilee Hills,  
Hyderabad - 500033  
India.
